export const data = [
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite thing?",
        option1: "Cony bunny",
        option2: "Cute sticker",
        option3: "Bed and blanket",
        option4: "Brush pens",
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite fruit?",
        option1: "Guava",
        option2: "Watermelon",
        option3: "Pineapple",
        option4: "Mango",
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex MBTI?",
        option1: "ENFP",
        option2: "ISTP",
        option3: "INTJ",
        option4: "ESTJ",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which is Ex favourite day of the week?",
        option1: "Tuesday",
        option2: "Thursday",
        option3: "Friday",
        option4: "Saturday",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which is Ex favourite breakfast?",
        option1: "Mayo egg sando",
        option2: "Shashuka with sourdough",
        option3: "Kaya toast with kopi",
        option4: "Cream cheese bagel with americano",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex biggest fear?",
        option1: "Needles",
        option2: "Blood",
        option3: "Bitter gourd",
        option4: "Ghost",
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite number?",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "7",
        option3: "69",
        option4: "911",
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite pasttime?",
        option1: "Photography",
        option2: "Hiking",
        option3: "Lepak at malls",
        option4: "Baking and cooking",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which is Ex favourite band?",
        option1: "One Republic",
        option2: "One Direction",
        option3: "5 Second of Summer",
        option4: "Chainsmoker",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite subject in high school?",
        option1: "Add Maths",
        option2: "Biology",
        option3: "Sejarah",
        option4: "Chemistry",
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What was Ex initial engineering major?",
        option1: "Chemical",
        option2: "Civil",
        option3: "Nah, she's a software since day one",
        option4: "Mechanical",
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite colour?",
        option1: "Ivy blue",
        option2: "Mint green",
        option3: "Purple",
        option4: "Yellow",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ex favourite language?",
        option1: "C++",
        option2: "JavaScript",
        option3: "Python",
        option4: "Java",
        answer: 4,
    },
]